<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>B3L7</title>
    <link>https://b3l7.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on B3L7</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 10:21:30 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://b3l7.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Lightless Beacon Recap</title>
      <link>https://b3l7.com/posts/lightlessbeacon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 10:21:30 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b3l7.com/posts/lightlessbeacon/</guid>
      <description>Introduction A few months ago my regular D&amp;amp;D 5E group decided we wanted to play a one shot of Call of Cthulhu for Halloween. Many of our players were also in a book club together in which we are doing several Lovecraft stories for Halloween so we thought the coinciding game would be a fun crossover. As the Dungeon Master of the group it fell to me to take on the mantle of the Keeper of Arcane Lore&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doom WAD: Reactor Core</title>
      <link>https://b3l7.com/posts/reactorcore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 14:15:31 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b3l7.com/posts/reactorcore/</guid>
      <description>Download: Reactor Core
Requirements: Doom 2, GZDoom
I created this WAD a few years ago with the aim to make a megawad of several levels with a continuous story. That seems unlikely now so I am releasing it as is so people can play around with it. You can see up front that I was more interested in interesting aesthetics over unique game play. That being said I learned a lot in the process and I think it helped set me down the road to eventually getting into game development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Searchers of the Unknown Omnibus v3</title>
      <link>https://b3l7.com/posts/sotuomnibusv3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 08:47:44 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b3l7.com/posts/sotuomnibusv3/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;catacomb&amp;rdquo;by begemot_dn is licensed under CC BY-NC 2.0

Searchers of the Unknown Omnibus v3 (PDF)
Searchers of the Unknown Omnibus v3 (ODT)
Last week I posted about my play test of the Searchers of the Unknown Omnibus using Temple of the Moon Priests. That session was enlightening and caused me to spend a lot of time thinking about SotU and the lessons I had learned. After talking to my players and many of you online, I decided to make some changes which culminated in version 3 of the Searchers of the Unknown Omnibus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>They Came From the Sky</title>
      <link>https://b3l7.com/posts/theycamefromthesky/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 09:00:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b3l7.com/posts/theycamefromthesky/</guid>
      <description>Note: I originaly wrote this story 4 years ago for /r/writingprompts
&amp;ldquo;Space Art Wallpapers 20&amp;rdquo;by en busca del bit perdido is licensed under CC BY-NC-SA 2.0

They came from the sky in a rain of fire and on that day the gods wept for they knew that we were doomed. You are asking me to describe them so do not blame me for the dread it will instill within you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temple of the Moon Priests with Searchers of the Unknown</title>
      <link>https://b3l7.com/posts/moonpriestssotu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 08:55:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b3l7.com/posts/moonpriestssotu/</guid>
      <description>Note: Unless otherwise noted the images in this post are from Temple of the Moon Priests by Will Doyle and Stacey Allan under Attribution-ShareAlike 3.0 (CC BY-SA 3.0 US) Last week I shared my edit of Searchers of the Unknown which I call the Searchers of the Unkown Omnibus. At the time I talked about my desire to play test the minimalist system. It seems fate saw it as a priority as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Song of Soil</title>
      <link>https://b3l7.com/posts/songofsoil/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 11:15:57 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b3l7.com/posts/songofsoil/</guid>
      <description>1
The Song of Soil We, the sand
animated with the fire of suns,
lay intertwined in love
beneath the stars of eternity,
knowing we were mortal,
and knowing,
that on our passing,
our soil
would lay fertile beds
for new growth
and the embers of our hearts
would be sparks to light new flames.
We,
the angry maelstroms,
raged battles
across our mindscapes
against the ghosts
of those who never really</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Searchers of the Unknown Omnibus</title>
      <link>https://b3l7.com/posts/sotuomnibus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 08:57:53 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b3l7.com/posts/sotuomnibus/</guid>
      <description>Searchers of the Unknown Omnibus (PDF)
Searchers of the Unknown Omnibus (ODT)
A friend of mine had been asking me for a few years now if we could play D&amp;amp;D. She has never played before and it got me thinking about the quickest and easiest way to introduce new players to tabletop roleplaying games.
I looked at HERE’S SOME FUCKIN’ D&amp;amp;D by Dustin R. I really liked the simplicity of it but felt the tone and mechanics were not quite what I was looking for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phaser 3 Tilemap Pack Update</title>
      <link>https://b3l7.com/posts/phaser3-tilemap-pack-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 14:43:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b3l7.com/posts/phaser3-tilemap-pack-update/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday I updated my Tilemap and Filepack Template to be compatible with Phaser 3.17, webpack 4, babel, and implemented pools for the player and enemy projectiles. I created the template a year ago and other than a minor compatibility update last fall haven&amp;rsquo;t touched it since.
Phaser 3 Tilemap &amp;amp; File Pack Project Template
Demo
The original idea of the template was to illustrate a concept I was trying to explain to another user over at HTML5GameDevs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://b3l7.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 16:08:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b3l7.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Indie Game Developer, Writer, &amp;amp; RPG Enthusiast.
E-Mail</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>