<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>One Page Dungeon on B3L7</title>
    <link>https://b3l7.com/tags/one-page-dungeon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in One Page Dungeon on B3L7</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 10:00:30 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://b3l7.com/tags/one-page-dungeon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Plumbing the Depths with Maze Rats</title>
      <link>https://b3l7.com/posts/plumbingdepths/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 10:00:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b3l7.com/posts/plumbingdepths/</guid>
      <description>Well we have a wacky one here kids! The group got together in between our normal campaign sessions to play a one-off and we finally got to check out a system I&amp;rsquo;ve been dying try for a while now. That system would of course be Maze Rats by Ben Milton. I wanted to pair this ultra-light system with a quick adventure so I opted again for a One Page Dungeon since the last one went so well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temple of the Moon Priests with Searchers of the Unknown</title>
      <link>https://b3l7.com/posts/moonpriestssotu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 08:55:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b3l7.com/posts/moonpriestssotu/</guid>
      <description>Last week I shared my edit of Searchers of the Unknown which I call the Searchers of the Unkown Omnibus. At the time I talked about my desire to play test the minimalist system. It seems fate saw it as a priority as well. The opportunity arose later in the week when it became clear that my regular 5e campaign would be missing several players for a climactic session. We decided that rather than have anyone miss out on a session we had been building to for a year that it would be better to run a one off game with whoever could make it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>