<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>D&amp;D on B3L7</title>
    <link>https://b3l7.com/tags/dd/</link>
    <description>Recent content in D&amp;D on B3L7</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 15:37:30 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://b3l7.com/tags/dd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Plumbing the Depths with Maze Rats</title>
      <link>https://b3l7.com/posts/plumbingdepths/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2019 15:37:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b3l7.com/posts/plumbingdepths/</guid>
      <description>Well we have a wacky one here kids! The group got together in between our normal campaign sessions to play a one-off and we finally got to check out a system I&amp;rsquo;ve been dying try for a while now. That system would of course be Maze Rats by Ben Milton. I wanted to pair this ultra-light system with a quick adventure so I opted again for a One Page Dungeon since the last one went so well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Searchers of the Unknown Omnibus v4</title>
      <link>https://b3l7.com/posts/sotuomnibusv4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 17:19:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b3l7.com/posts/sotuomnibusv4/</guid>
      <description>Searchers of the Unknown Omnibus v4 (PDF)
Searchers of the Unknown Omnibus v4 (ODT)
This is a minor update to my Searchers of the Unknown Omnibus. Changes include:
 Removed Encounter Movement Penalty for shields Nerfed bonuses for Races and Classes as I think they were excessive Added bonus for stealth and stunts for thieves Various minor fixes and tweaks  
Version 3 of the Omnibus can still be found here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Searchers of the Unknown Omnibus v3</title>
      <link>https://b3l7.com/posts/sotuomnibusv3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 08:47:44 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b3l7.com/posts/sotuomnibusv3/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;catacomb&amp;rdquo;by begemot_dn is licensed under CC BY-NC 2.0

Update: Version 4 is available here
Searchers of the Unknown Omnibus v3 (PDF)
Searchers of the Unknown Omnibus v3 (ODT)
Last week I posted about my play test of the Searchers of the Unknown Omnibus using Temple of the Moon Priests. That session was enlightening and caused me to spend a lot of time thinking about SotU and the lessons I had learned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Temple of the Moon Priests with Searchers of the Unknown</title>
      <link>https://b3l7.com/posts/moonpriestssotu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 08:55:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b3l7.com/posts/moonpriestssotu/</guid>
      <description>Note: Unless otherwise noted the images in this post are from Temple of the Moon Priests by Will Doyle and Stacey Allan under Attribution-ShareAlike 3.0 (CC BY-SA 3.0 US) Last week I shared my edit of Searchers of the Unknown which I call the Searchers of the Unkown Omnibus. At the time I talked about my desire to play test the minimalist system. It seems fate saw it as a priority as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Searchers of the Unknown Omnibus</title>
      <link>https://b3l7.com/posts/sotuomnibus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 08:57:53 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://b3l7.com/posts/sotuomnibus/</guid>
      <description>Update: Version 4 is available here

Searchers of the Unknown Omnibus (PDF)
Searchers of the Unknown Omnibus (ODT)
A friend of mine had been asking me for a few years now if we could play D&amp;amp;D. She has never played before and it got me thinking about the quickest and easiest way to introduce new players to tabletop roleplaying games.
I looked at HERE’S SOME FUCKIN’ D&amp;amp;D by Dustin R.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>